Over there... No, not you.
过去那边...不, 你不去
Sit down, all of you.
坐下, 你们全部
Incredible. You fooled me the first time we met,
不可思议．我们第一次碰面时你骗过了我...
but now, even Salamander himself
would think he was looking in a mirror.
看看现在, 就算 Salamander 他自己也会以为他在照镜子
Why? You want this man to impersonate Salamander, why?
为什么？你想让这个人假冒 Salamander, 为什么？
How much are they paying you?
他们付给你多少钱？
I beg your pardon?
你说什么？
They want you to assassinate Salamander,
don't they? Take his place?
他们想让你刺杀 Salamander, 对吧？取而代之？
That's ridiculous! I couldn't possibly do that.
简直荒唐！我不可能干出这种事情
But you were preparing to impersonate him, weren't you?
但你早就在准备假冒他, 是吧？
Well well, yes.
噢好吧, 是的
Alright then, why?
那好了, 为什么？
Because Salamander holds my two friends prisoner
and I was going to attempt to rescue them.
因为 Salamander 关押了我的两个朋友, 我是打算营救他们
And at the same time get evidence
that would expose Salamander...
与此同时，找到证据, 可以用来揭发 Salamander...
...as a traitor, blackmailer and murderer!
...证明他是个卖国贼, 勒索犯, 凶手！
Quite an ambitious plan.
How do you know such evidence exists?
计划很有野心嘛．你怎么知道这种证据存在呢？
It exists in Salamander's records.
它存在于 Salamander 的档案室
Oh, yes, I know why you want Salamander out of the way.
哦, 是的, 我知道你为什么要除掉 Salamander
You hate him because he exposed
your profitable sideline of misusing public money.
你恨他, 因为他揭露了你那盈利颇丰的副业是挪用公款办的
Oh, it was Salamander who was misusing the money.
噢, Salamander 才是挪用公款的人
And I was dismissed from my post and
the evidence against Salamander concealed.
然后我就被从位子上赶下来, 对 Salamander 不利的证据就不见了
So you say. But you've no evidence at all
against Salamander, have you?
这是你的说法．但你没有针对 Salamander 的任何证据, 有吗？
I tell you the evidence is in Salamander's records.
我告诉你证据就在 Salamander 的档案室
And I'm expected to take that from you?
而你就指望我信了你的邪?
We do hold evidence...
我们的确有证据...
that Salamander isn't quite
so pure and white as he's painted.
证明 Salamander 并不像他自己所粉刷的那么清白
No? What?
不清白？什么证据？
A file, containing certain information
about a gentleman called Fedorin.
一份文件, 里面有关于一位叫 Fedorin 的先生的一些信息
Salamander was going to
use this evidence against Fedorin.
Salamander 本打算用这个证据来对付 Fedorin
Blackmail him into submission.
after he'd got rid of Denes, that is.
勒索他逼他就范 — 就在他除掉 Denes 之后
And so gain control of another zone.
这样就可以得到又一个区的控制权
Where is this file?
这份文件在哪里？
Fariah has it, Salamander's food taster.
Fariah 手上, Salamander 的食物品尝员
Fariah? But she's dead.
Fariah? 但她已经死了
Dead? But how?
死了？怎么死的？
She was shot by one of Benik's guards, escaping arrest.
她被 Benik 的一个警卫击中了, 在逃避追捕的时候
Escaping arrest? Benik had her killed,
逃避追捕？是 Benik 让人杀了她
because she had evidence against Salamander.
因为她有 Salamander 的证据
And Benik will return the file to Salamander.
然后 Benik 会把文件交回给 Salamander
We must get to the Research Station.
我们必须赶到研究站去
You're not going anywhere or doing anything.
你哪儿也不能去, 什么也不能做
As far as I'm concerned, this story you've told me
could be a pack of lies...
就我看来, 你告诉我的这个故事可能只是一堆谎言...
to cover your attempt to assassinate Salamander.
只为了给你企图刺杀 Salamander 找借口
Now I'm not saying I'm altogether satisfied with
Salamander or his organisation,
我现在倒不是说我全然赞同 Salamander 和他的安排
but I'll investigate in my own way.
但我会用自己的方式进行调查
Meanwhile Salamander will have found a way to cover himself,
与此同时 Salamander 会找到方法为他自己打掩护
and also a way of disposing of you.
You're digging your own grave, Bruce.
还能找到方法干掉你．你是在自掘坟墓, Bruce
That's my affair. And I do things my own way.
那是我的事．我做事情有我自己的方法
And I do things my way.
而我也有我的方法
Really, as Head of Security,
you should have more reliable guards.
真的, 作为安全主管, 你应该有一些更可靠的护卫
- Leader Salamander?
- Still inside, sir.
- Salamander 领袖呢？ - 还在里面, 长官
Let me know the moment the doors are opened.
门打开的时候通知我
Yes sir.
好的长官
So you've brought them?
Good. Any trouble?
看来你把他们带过来了?  很好, 遇到麻烦没？
No, a light drug saw to that.
没．一小颗药片就搞定了
Let me know the moment they wake up.
他们醒来的时候通知我
Yes sir.
好的长官
I'm looking forward to questioning them.
I have the feeling they're going to be stubborn.
我很期待能审讯他们．我有一种感觉他们会很顽固
So much more interesting when our prisoners are stubborn.
我们的囚犯很顽固的时候, 乐趣就多了
You're only making trouble for yourself.
Killing me won't get you anywhere.
你这只是在给自己找麻烦．杀了我不会给你带来任何好处
We have to get to the Research Station,
and you're not going to stop us.
我们必须赶去研究站, 你不能阻止我们
But you're completely surrounded.
但你们被完全包围了
You don't really believe I came here
with just one guard, do you?
你不会真的相信我只带了一个警卫就过来了吧, 是吗？
You'd be very silly to try and fight your way out.
你要是想试着硬闯出去就太傻了
I'd give you about... thirty seconds to live if you try.
我会让你们活大约...30秒，你们不妨一试
Alright Bruce, we might have just thirty seconds
好了 Bruce, 我们可能只有 30 秒
but you'd have exactly half that time, if you were lucky!
但你只有那一半时间, 还得运气好！
Please, Mister Kent!
You're forgetting one very important thing.
请了, Kent 先生！你忘了一件非常重要的事情
- What?  - Me.
什么？  - 我
Without me you haven't got an earthly chance
of getting in that control centre.
没有我的话, 你进入那个控制中心的机会一丁点也没有
So?
怎样？
I told you before,
I will not have anything to do with violence!
我早跟你说过, 我不会跟暴力扯上关系！
And what about your two friends?
那你的两个朋友怎么办？
Are you going to leave them
to the tender mercies of Salamander?
你就打算让他们俩完全指望 Salamander 的仁慈？
No I am not. May I?
不, 我不会．可以吗？
- What?  - Please? Just trust me.
- 怎么？ - 拜托？尽管相信我
Now then, I think you agree that
at this moment your life is in my hands.
现在, 我想你会同意, 目前你的性命在我的手上
What are you doing?
你要做什么？
Hold it.
拿住它
It's alright, Mister Bruce isn't going
to shoot anyone, are you?
没事的, Bruce 先生不会朝任何人开枪的, 对吗？
Why? Why'd you do that?
为什么？为什么你要这么做？
Because I think I know what sort of man you are
- honest and reasonable.
因为我觉得我知道你是哪种人 - 诚实而理性
Go on.
继续
I gave you back that gun because I trust you.
Now I want you to trust me.
我把枪还给你是因为我相信你．现在我要你也相信我
You must be a complete fool, or very clever.
你肯定是个完全的傻子, 或者是极其聪明
Well I'm afraid you will have to
make up your mind to that right away.
那, 恐怕你必须得立刻打定主意
What do you hope to gain from this gesture?
你摆这个姿态是期望获得什么？
Your confidence.
你的信心
Do you believe Kent's accusations against Salamander?
你相信 Kent 对 Salamander 的控诉吗？
I think there's reasonable doubt about
Salamander's personal integrity,
我觉得 Salamander 正直与否是存在一定程度的疑问的
but there's only one way to get proof.
但只有一个办法获得证据
By getting into Salamander's Research Station?
得先闯入 Salamander 的研究站？
Yes. And my two young friends may have some information.
是的．而且我的两个年轻朋友也可能有些信息
And if there isn't any evidence?
但如果没有任何证据呢？
Then you'll be perfectly free to arrest us
and put us in prison, won't you?
那你就完全可以逮捕我们, 把我们扔进监狱, 行吗？
Alright, I'll do it, on one condition.
好吧, 我干了．但有一个条件
And what's that?
什么条件？
That you and I go alone,
Kent and the girl stay here as hostages.
就是你和我单独去, 而 Kent 和这个女孩在这里做人质
No wait a minute, I must go with him.
不, 等一下, 我必须跟他一起去
No, Kent, you stay here.
I must be mad to trust you.
不, Kent, 你必须呆在这里．我要是相信你就是疯了
I only hope your impersonation of Salamander fools Benik.
我只是期望你假冒的 Salamander 能骗过 Benik
If it doesn't, we're in dead trouble.
如果没有, 咱俩都麻烦大了
Here, take this. Keep those two in the caravan.
来, 拿着这个．让他俩呆在车里
Oh, and, um, watch the girl. Come on.
噢, 对了, 看好这个女孩儿．来吧
Ah, how we getting on here, huh?
Ah, all this? That's a good haul.
啊, 我们进展如何，哈？这些都是？收获不少嘛
Stand by to make your report, Swann.
准备开始做你的报告, Swaan
Reaching full power here, Swann.
这里已经达到最大功率, Swaan
Salamander, I must see you.
Salamander, 我必须见你
Not now, we are too busy.
现在不行, 我们太忙了
This is urgent.
这事很紧急
Oh very well.
噢, 好吧
Now what's the matter, huh?
现在说说, 什么事, 哈？
What's this? What is this?
这是什么？这是什么？
What?
什么？
Newspaper. It's a piece of newspaper.
报纸．这是一张报纸
So?
怎么？
Well go on, look at it. Read it. Last year's date.
继续, 看一眼眼, 读一下．日期是去年
Look at the bit of headline there. THERE!
看看那里的头条, 那里！
Control yourself, Swann. You'll go mad.
控制一下自己, Swann, 你这是要疯了
"Holiday Liner Sinks"!
"假日航线沉没＂！
You say there's a global war. Radiation everywhere.
你说有一场全球战争, 到处都是辐射
How can there be holiday liners? Tell me how!
怎么会有假日航线呢？告诉我怎么会！
You've lied to us, haven't you? HAVEN'T YOU?
你对我们撒谎了, 有没有？有没有？
In a way, Swann, yes. I had to.
某种程度上, Swann, 算是吧．我迫不得已
Had to? What do you mean had to?
不得已？你什么意思, 不得已？
Well it's true that... that the war is over,
嗯, 的确是...战争已经结束了
but have you any idea what happens to people
who've been involved in a nuclear war? HAVE YOU?
但卷入核战争的人会怎样你有概念吗？有吗？
Course I haven't, I've been down here.
我当然没有, 我都在这下面
Those who are lucky enough to escape the annihilation
have their bodies eaten away by radiation poisoning.
那些侥幸捡了一命的人, 身体却难逃辐射的毒害
They're deformed in mind and body.
他们在精神和身体上都是畸形
But this, this, this newspaper?
但这个, 这个, 这份报纸呢？
They have a kind of society,
but it's... it's evil! Corrupt!
他们有着某种社会, 但它是...它是邪恶的！堕落的！
You don't think I could expose you to that sort of thing?
你不会认为我会让你们去接触那种东西吧？
Think of Mary and the other women.
想想 Mary 和其他女人
You could have told me, at least.
你本可以告诉我的, 至少
I decided not to.
我决定了不告诉
You should have told me.
你应该告诉我的
I thought it was best.
我想那是最好的
And what about the natural disasters
we've been organising?
那我们一直在制造的自然灾害是怎么回事？
The volcanoes, earthquakes?
那些火山, 地震？
Swann, they're not fit to live.
Swann, 它们不适合居住
You're murdering them, killing them off!
你在谋杀他们, 残害生命！
I want you and the others
to inherit the Earth, make a new world.
我想让你和其他人继承地球, 创造一个新世界
Yes, I know all about that,
but not at the price of wholesale murder!
是的, 这我都知道, 但不是以大批谋杀为代价！
It's not murder! If you could see
you would understand. It's an act of mercy.
这不是谋杀！如果你见了你就会明白, 这是仁慈之举
There must be some other way.
肯定有其它的办法的
NO!
没有！
I won't take your word any more.
I want to see for myself.
我不再相信你的话了, 我要自己去看
You, you, you'd be horrified.
你, 你, 你会吓坏的
Maybe.
可能
The radiation would kill you!
辐射会杀死你
I'll chance that.
我会赌一把
Very well. But, but promise me one thing,
you won't tell the others.
好吧．但是, 答应我一件事, 你不会告诉其他人
Why shouldn't I?
为什么我不会？
Because I am right and you are wrong!
因为我是对的, 你是错的！
You, you wouldn't want to,
you wouldn't want to hurt them like that, huh?
你, 你不会愿意, 你不会愿意伤害他们那样的人的, 哈？
And if you're lying,
and I want to tell when I get back...?
但如果你是在撒谎, 等我回来我就会告诉他们...
How can I stop you?
我怎么能阻止你呢？
You'd better, ah, tell them you're coming with me.
你最好...告诉他们你要跟我一起去
Say er, say you've persuaded me.
就说, 呃, 说你说服了我
Swann, trust me, don't go ahead with this huh?
Swann, 相信我, 别继续这事, 嗯？
I have to.
我必须去
Where are we?
我们在哪儿？
You're in the Australasian zone.
I had you brought here especially.
你在澳洲区, 我特意让人带你们过来的
Why?
为什么？
So that Salamander could ask you some questions.
以便 Salamander 可以问你一些问题
For all the answers he's gonna get
he might as well have left us there.
就为了得到那些答案的话，他也可以把我们留在那里
Stand up when you talk to me!
跟我说话的时候站起来！
You'll get nowhere by shouting.
你大声嚷嚷也得不到什么
On the contrary. I'm going to get everything
I want from you two.
恰恰相反, 我会从你俩这里得到一切
We'll not tell you a thing.
我们不会告诉你任何事情
That's good. I like that.
这样很好, 我喜欢这样
- What?  - Spirit. Resistance.
- 什么？  - 斗志, 顽强
You've got plenty of both, haven't you, boy?
这两样你都很充足, 是吗, 小子？
Well I wonder how long you'll last.
Five minutes?
我好奇你能撑多久？5分钟？
No, a little longer, maybe? Ten, perhaps?
不, 会长点儿, 可能不？10分钟, 也许？
- What do you mean?
- Come now, you don't think...
- 你什么意思?  - 得了, 你不会认为...
...I'm just going to sit here
and ask questions, do you?
...我会干坐在这里问你问题吧, 是吗？
You must have been a nasty little boy.
你以前一定是一个令人讨厌的小男孩儿
Oh I was. But I had a very enjoyable childhood.
哦, 我是．但我有一个相当愉悦的童年
Ha ha hah. Yes, I thought so.
Spirit, plenty of spirit.
哈哈哈, 是的, 我猜也是．斗志, 昂扬的斗志
Oh, we're going to enjoy ourselves, aren't we? Now then...
哦, 我们会一起享受的, 对不？现在...
I... I thought you were going to take us to see Salamander?
我...我记得你是打算带我们去见 Salamander 吧?
Yes I will. But he'd expect me to do my little best first.
是, 我会的．但他期望我先尽我自己努力
You lay a finger on her, I'll kill you.
你动她一根手指头, 我就会宰了你
Will you? How? Ha ha ha.
你会吗？怎么宰？哈哈哈
No. I think the time's come for you
to answer my questions, don't you?
不, 我觉得现在轮到你来回答我的问题了, 对不？
Come here, girl!
过来, 女孩儿！
If you don't, I shall have to shoot one of you.
如果你不过来, 我就会朝你们其中一个开枪了
Oh, not a mortal wound. In the leg, perhaps?
哦, 不是马上会死的那种．射在腿上, 也许是？
Better go. Don't worry.
赶紧走, 别担心
There. That's better.
对啦, 这好多了
Oh, such pretty hair, don't you think?
哦, 多漂亮的头发啊, 你不觉得吗？
Alright, leave her alone. What do want to know?
好吧, 放开她．你想知道什么？
Quite a lot. And you're going to
tell me everything. Aren't you?
很多．你会告诉我所有事情吧, 会吗？
- Aaah!  - All right, yes!
- 啊！ - 好了, 行！
Who's behind you? Is it Giles Kent?
你们后面是谁？是 Giles Kent 吗？
Oh, so they're here, eh?
哦, 那他们在这里了, 嗯？
Salamander, I, I thought you were in Records?
Salamander, 我..我记得你还在档案室?
Have they told you anything yet?
他们告诉你什么没有？
Not yet.
还没有
Very well. Bruce and I will take over.
很好, Burce 和我接手吧
You may go, and er,
take your little puppy dog with you, hm?
你可以走了, 呃, 带走你的小狗行吗, 嗯？
Now...
现在...
We can't tell you anything.
我们告诉不了你什么
Of course not. We know everything.
当然不能．我们知道所有事情
We know about Giles Kent,
我们知道 Giles Kent 的事
we know about the girl called Astrid,
我们知道那个叫 Astrid 的女孩儿的事
and we know about your friend the Doctor.
我们还知道你们的朋友 - 博士的事
I don't believe you.
我不相信
A childish plan to impersonate me.
Yes the truth, isn't it?
冒充我是个幼稚的计划．这是实话吧, 对不？
Ah but he didn't agree to it.
是, 但他没有同意
But you two were sent to
the Central European zone to stir up trouble.
但你俩被派往了中欧区, 想把水搅浑
If you want to know the truth,
如果你们要知道实情
Giles Kent told us a story and we weren't sure.
Giles Kent 跟我们说了一个故事, 但我们并不确定
Before the Doctor could do anything
在博士采取任何行动之前
we had to come here
and find out what person you were like.
我们必须到这里来, 弄明白你是什么样的人
Yeah, and we found that out right enough.
是, 而且我们发现的情况够多的
You see Bruce, they just terrorists.
Not very big fry, either.
你看 Bruce, 他们只是恐怖分子．不是什么大鱼
All this nonsense about proof against me.
一直叨叨着所谓针对我的证据
If you're doing so much good for the world,
why are you so afraid for your own life?
如果你为世界做了如此多的贡献, 你为什么会如此担心你自己的性命？
Aye, and why do you have so many enemies?
是．而你为什么有这么多的敌人？
- Personal guards?
- Your own food taster?
- 私人保镖？  - 你自己的食物品尝员？
And why destroy the one man
people trusted, Alexander Denes?
为什么还毁掉一个人们信任的人, Alexander Denes?
- Aye.  - What do you mean, destroy?
- 是  - 你什么意思, ＂毁掉＂？
One of your men shot him.
你一个手下枪杀了他
Trying to escape?
他试图逃走？
He shot him deliberately.
他蓄意开枪的
Aye. And that girl Fariah,
well she was close to Salamander,
是．还有 Fariah 那个女孩儿, 她与 Salamander 关系如此之近
she'd speak against him, I know she would.
还是会出言反对他, 我知道她会的
Fariah is dead.
Fariah 已经死了
Dead?
死了？
You've had her murdered too, have you?
你把她也谋杀了, 是吗？
- Why you...
- Oh, Victoria! Don't hit me!
- 为什么你...  - 哦, Victoria! 别打我！
You wouldn't hit your old friend the Doctor, would you?
你不会打你的老朋友博士的, 是吧？
I wouldn't leave you in the tender mercy of Salamander.
我不会把你们扔下，任凭 Salamander 乱来的
You're the Doctor?
你是博士？
You don't believe me? Oh. Huh.
你不相信我？噢, 哈
Only, you made me leave it in the TARDIS.
只是, 你让我把它留在 TARDIS 里面了
- It is him!  - Oh, Doctor!
- 真是他！ - 哦, 博士！
"Tardis"? "Tardis", what's that?
"TARDIS"? "TARDIS" 是什么？
Well, it's a little place that we three have in common.
哦, 只是我们三人共同熟悉的一个小地方
You must admit they thought
I was Salamander to begin with.
你必须承认他们一开始把我认做了 Salamander
Yes. I concede that. But there's still no proof.
是的, 我承认．但还是没有见到证据
No, but there's enough doubt in your mind...
没有, 但你脑袋里面已经有了足够的疑问了吧
to make you go on asking questions, isn't there?
That's why we came here.
你想问很多问题, 是不？这就是为什么我们来这里
Wait. What happens up there?
等等．上面什么情况？
Oh, it ends in a ruined building.
This is where I bring the stores,
噢, 前面倒塌的建筑，没路了．这是我带储备来的地方
- uh, you would be safer here.
- Safer?
- 你在这里会安全些  - 安全些?
Yes, the radiation.
I don't think it filters down here.
是的, 因为辐射．我觉得还没有渗透到这里来
I still want to see the surface.
我还是想去看看地表
You will, you will.
你会看到的, 你会的
I should have insisted on going with him.
Bruce should have taken me.
我应该坚持跟他一起去的．Bruce 应该带上我
You know he doesn't trust you.
你知道他并不信任你
He wouldn't trust his own grandmother.
他连他自己的祖母都不信任
Oh, never mind, Giles. We've come a long way.
噢, 别管了, Giles. 我们走了好远了
Months ago, well a few weeks ago even,
nobody would have even listened to you.
几个月以前, 噢甚至几个星期以前, 没人肯听你的
Oh, maybe.
噢, 也许吧
There's no maybe about it.
这并不是什么也许
Yeah perhaps you're right.
Bruce listens to us at last.
是, 也许你是对的．Bruce 最终肯听我们说了
He's even prepared to ask questions, that's fine, but...
他甚至打算问问题了, 这很好, 但是...
I know Salamander.
He'd talk his way out of the quicksand.
我了解 Salamander．他陷进流沙都能靠一张嘴出来
Well what else can we do,
the guard's still outside?
那我们还能做什么, 警卫都还在外面？
I must get into the Research Centre.
我必须进入研究中心
I've got to make sure that Bruce
understands the evidence, understands it, Astrid.
我得确保 Bruce 能理解这个证据, 理解它, Astrid
Don't you realize, he mightn't know
what he's looking for. I know.
你没有意识到吗, 他可能不知道他要找什么．而我知道
But we can't attack the guard.
It would only make matters worse.
但我们不能袭击警卫．这只会让事情变得更糟
Not if I was to give Bruce real evidence.
不会, 我会给 Bruce 真正的证据
Giles, how long would it take you
to get to the Research Station?
Giles, 你赶去研究站要多久？
Well just a few minutes, I've got a pass.
It's just a matter of getting there.
噢, 只要几分钟．我有通行证, 只是赶到那里的问题
Alright, I think I can help you.
好了, 我想我可以帮你
I'll draw the guard off and leave you alone.
我去把警卫引开, 单独留你在这里
You think you can do it?
你觉得你可以做到？
Yes, I think so.
是的, 我觉得可以
But I thought you said we weren't going to attack the guard?
但我记得你说过我们不打算袭击警卫？
Oh, we're not going to attack the guard,
噢, 我们不会去袭击警卫
but there is going to be an attack. A fatal one.
但还是会有一次袭击, 致命的一次
Where does this lead?
那通向哪里？
It goes on up and comes out in a field.
它往上走, 出口在一片空地上
What about radiation?
辐射怎样？
Here it's almost negligible.
这个地方基本可以忽略
You mean you could have brought others here from below?
你是说你可以把其他人从下面带到这里来？
I don't understand you.
我搞不懂你
Don't you realise what a break
it would be for them,
难道你没意识到, 这将对他们来说是个多大的突破？
just moving away from that underground tomb once in a while?
只要隔一段时间能够从那个地下坟墓逃离一下？
You seem to forget, Swann,
I've brought people up here before!
你似乎忘了, Swaan, 我之前带人上来过！
There's always an element of risk!
总是会有某种危险存在的！
I still want to have a look at these people
you say are living on the surface.
我还是想看一眼你说的那些住在地表的人
Where does that lead?
那边通向哪里？
Oh, that's a dead end.
It's a place I sometimes rest.
哦, 那是条死路．我有时候在那里休息
It's very hard work, you know, bringing all the...
真的很辛苦的, 知道吗, 带着所有这些...
Yes, I know that.
This way, then?
是的, 我知道这个．那边呢？
You, you sure you... won't change your mind, huh?
你, 你确定...不改变主意了, 哈？
What's going on here?
这里什么情况？
He's been shot. Through the window.
他中枪了．从窗外射进来的
Alright, stand back.
好吧，往后站
He's finished.
他完蛋了
Better get a doctor anyway, just in case.
最好还是找个医生, 以防万一
Hey! Come back!
嘿！回来！
Hellllp! Somebody help me.
救命！谁来救救我
Heeellllp! Help... Somebody help me...
救-命-！救命...谁来救救我！
Who did this to you?
谁把你这样了？
A man named... Salamander.
一个叫做...Salamander 的人
Salamander?
Salamander?﻿